我并不想把你当做下人
I don't wish to treat you as inferior.
但你却命令我跟你说话
Yet you'd command me to speak?
我命令的口吻伤了你的自尊吗
Are you very hurt by my tone of command?
很少有主人会去关心
There are few masters who'd trouble to enquire
自己的言语是否中伤了
whether their paid subordinates
他花钱雇来的这些仆人
were hurt by their commands.
花钱雇来的仆人
Paid subordinate?
我倒忘记了薪酬的事
I'd forgotten the salary.
那么从雇佣的角度来说
Well, on that mercenary ground,
你是否愿意与我平等地谈话
will you consent to speak as my equal
而不把它当做是傲慢无礼的要求呢
without thinking that the request arises from insolence?
我绝不会把不拘礼节错当傲慢无理  先生
I'd never mistake informality for insolence, sir.
前者是我所喜欢的
One, I rather like.